thetotaltakeover.com 2016-03-14

# 

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how “www.TheTotalTakeOver.com” uses and protects  
any information that you give “www.TheTotalTakeOver.com” when you use this  
website. 

THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO SHARING USERNAME/PASSWORD WITH “BUSINESS PARTNERS”, FRIENDS, EMPLOYEES, OR ANY OTHER PERSON THAT HAS NOT PURCHASED THE RIGHTS TO THE INFORMATION IN The Total Take Over. If a person does it will result in an immediate ban from all information with absolutely no REFUND. There IS A NO REFUND POLICY ASSOCIATED WITH The Total Take Over. There is ALSO NO LETTING PEOPLE IN FOR FREE. ANY MEMBER CAUGHT DOING SO WILL BE TERMINATED AND BANNED FROM THE SYSTEM. The Total Take Over has a ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY FOR THIS. The Total Take Over has the right to delete/destroy any membership for any reason at any time if we feel there is foul play going on.

ALL TRAINING MATERIAL AND SOFTWARES ARE PROPERTY OF THE TOTAL TAKE OVER AND MAY NOT BE REUSED, RESOLD, OR IN ANY OTHER WAY USED WITHOUT THE EXPRESS WRITTEN CONSENT OF THE TOTAL TAKE OVER. Your use of the The Total Take Over Material displayed on/within the Site, or any other content on the Site, except as provided in these Terms of Use, is strictly prohibited.

(‘TTT’ and ‘we’ refers to The Total Takeover, owner of this website)

TTT is committed to keeping all your personal details safe and secure. My privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Collecting Your Personal Information

TTT is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that I collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We will not pass on your details to any third party and do not send out marketing e-mails to customers unless they have registered to receive such material, purchased from me, or downloaded one of my free or paid products.

The type of information We ‘may’ collect about you includes:

Your full name  
Your e-mail address  
Your postal address  
Your Phone Number

Generally, this information is requested when you are either downloading free products, when you purchase any of my products (Videos, software etc.), or when you subscribe to my newsletters. TTT will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information We hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that We hold about you by e-mailing us at Support@thetotaltakeover.com. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

How We Use Your Personal Information

Your personal information is used for four main purposes and they are as follows:

1\. To send out information, recommendations and resources to you.

2\. To provide assistance to you after you have purchased products from me.

3\. To help TTT create and deliver content most relevant to you.

4\. To enlighten you about new products, services, tool, upgrades, special offers and information which I feel may be of use to you.

We will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on www.TheTotalTakeOver.com

(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of www.TheTotalTakeOver.com;

(c) Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of www.TheTotalTakeOver.com.
